<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Manoj Sapkota</title>
    <link>http://manojsapkota.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Manoj Sapkota</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Manoj Sapkota</copyright><atom:link href="http://manojsapkota.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>http://manojsapkota.github.io/hobbies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://manojsapkota.github.io/hobbies/</guid>
      <description>I am Manoj Sapkota, Genomics Postdoc at Breeding Insight in Cornell University. I am passionate about plant breeding, genetics, genomics and bioinformatics. I call myself a grounded and solution-oriented plant scientist with wide variety of research experiences. I possess 6 plus years of experience in bioinformatics, statistics, plant breeding, traditional gene cloning, QTL mapping, molecular cloning, and gene editing. I am adept at motivating self and others. I am also highly organized, detail oriented and capable of taking leadership role to carry out assigned projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My CV and Resume</title>
      <link>http://manojsapkota.github.io/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://manojsapkota.github.io/cv/</guid>
      <description>My CV You can find my CV here.
My Resume You can find my resume here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>http://manojsapkota.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://manojsapkota.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>My Publications You can also check my Google Scholar Profile.
2024 Zhao D., Sapkota M., Bassil N., Mengist M.F., Iorizzo M., Heller-Uszynska, Molinari M., Beil C., and Sheehan M.J. A public mid-density genotyping platform for Blueberry (Vaccinium corymbosum L.), Genetic Resources. https://doi.org/10.46265/genresj.WQZS1824
Zhao D., Sapkota M., Lin M., Beil C., Sheehan M.J., Greene S., and Irish B., Genetic diversity, population structure, and taxonomic confirmation in annual medic (Medicago spp.) collection from Crimea, Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
